[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":30992,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":638160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6< /sub>, y ou start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":7994,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":646157,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2388,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":648548,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4048,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":652598,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1844,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":654443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5490,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":659936,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1321,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":661259,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2833,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":664093,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1470,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":665565,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum i s 6 or b igger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4089,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":669655,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":4305,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":673961,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6672,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":680634,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1231,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":681867,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2337,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":684205,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1805,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":686011,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember,  to perfo rm +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2445,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":688457,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1540,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":689999,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3037,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":693037,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1135,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":694173,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2507,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":696681,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":8654,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":705337,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":13479,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":718821,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Si milarly,  3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":23752,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":742577,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3189,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":745769,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1429,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":747200,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of  an elem ent is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2819,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":750020,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1193,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":751214,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["2","3"],"rt":3453,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":754671,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2778,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":757450,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":6799,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":764251,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1019,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":765272,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>?  <br /><b r /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2755,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":768028,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2423,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":770453,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":10647,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":781103,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We  have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":24746,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":805851,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element whi ch can m ake every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":10479,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":816332,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":2778,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":819112,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2475,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":821589,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect.  5 is a  generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":10750,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":832340,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":11704,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":844046,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 =  4 +<sub> 6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":7453,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":851501,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2959,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":854462,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1197,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":855659,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on  the num bers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":6569,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":862229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":6710,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":868943,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1011,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":869956,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is  3 +<sub> 9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3006,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":872963,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4740,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":877705,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3262,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":880969,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2763,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":883733,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2227,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":885962,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2933,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":888897,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3482,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":892381,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9 because thats what you get back to 0 with","response_history":["9 because thats what you get back to 0 with"],"rt":61109,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":953492,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":5223,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":958718,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2163,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":960882,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2069,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":962952,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no you cant get 1 3 5","response_history":["no you cant get 1 2","no you cant get 1 3 5"],"rt":28467,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":991420,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"you can get 0-9 using 3","response_history":["ye","y","3= 3, 3","you can get 1-","you can get 1","you can get 0-9 useing 2","you can get 0-9 useing 3","you can get 0-9 using 3"],"rt":144233,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1135657,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no you cant get all numbers","response_history":["no you cant get all numbers"],"rt":16472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1152133,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, i cant get many numbers","response_history":["no, i cant get many numbers"],"rt":27157,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1179292,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":12297,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1191592,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n = +_n - 1","response_history":["+_n ","n = 1 -","n = 1 ","n = 1","n = +_n - 1"],"rt":47136,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1238731,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Ple ase expl ain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n = +_n - x you need to take away n value from x so it totals to n","response_history":["inverse of x = x ","inverse of x = x","inverse of x = ","inverse of x = +_n - x you need to take away n value from x so it totals to n","n = +_n - x you need to take away n value from x so it totals to n"],"rt":53257,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1291990,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"i really dont see a pattern, i think this concept is still confusing","response_history":["i really dont see a pattern, i think this concept is still ocnuf","i really dont see  a patte rn, i think this concept is still confusing"],"rt":139209,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1431201,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":7612,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1438818,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":4679,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1443499,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n. ","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":12705,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1456205,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"no, because then 2/4 would more often be generator","response_history":["no, because then 2/4 would more often be generatior","no, because then 2/4 would more often be generatir","no, because then 2/4 would more often be generatr","no, because then 2/4 would more often be generator"],"rt":43665,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1499873,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is  its inv erse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":104912,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1604788,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"no, because if 1 was a generator, then 2 would always be, so it's sometimes","response_history":["no, because if 1 was a generati","no, because if 1 was a generator, then 1","no, because if 1 was a generator, then 2 would b","no, because if 1 was a generator, then 2 would always be, so it's co","no, because if 1 was a generator, then 2 would al ways be,  so it's c","no, because if 1 was a generator, then 2 would always be, so it's sometimes"],"rt":56884,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1661675,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":15933,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1677612,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1857,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1679471,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"29","response_history":["29"],"rt":2544,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1682017,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":3077,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1685094,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"calc for business college","response_history":[" cakc","cak","calc for bui","calc for business college"],"rt":12083,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1697179,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":5299,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1702480,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it u sed or e xplained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":4842,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1707325,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3159,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1710486,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["3 - definitely","2  - somew hat"],"rt":3659,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1714146,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2235,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1716383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2721,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1719106,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Engli sh","response_history":["English"],"rt":4115,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1723222,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":2589,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1725814,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":2133,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1727948,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]